[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Monty Pythons Life of Brian, how many people of Regs group wouldnt gladly give their lives to get rid of the Romans once and for all?", "correct_answer": "One", "incorrect_answers": ["Three", "Two", "None"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Phoenicia was an ancient civilization that spread maritime trade over the Mediterranean Sea. From where did the Phoenicians originate?", "correct_answer": "Modern day Liban (Sidon, Tyre)", "incorrect_answers": ["North Africa (Tunis, Algier)", "Sicily (Syracuse)", "Greek islands on the Aegean Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sense helps kiwis find food in the dark?", "correct_answer": "Sense of smell", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Eyesight", "Hearing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these can be defined as a clones biological mother and father?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The egg cell donor and the surrogate mother", "The egg cell donor and the surrogate mother", "The genetic material donor and the egg cell donor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which element is number two in the periodic table, following hydrogen?", "correct_answer": "Helium", "incorrect_answers": ["Carbon", "Lithium", "Oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which scientist discovered the atmosphere of Venus?", "correct_answer": "Mikhail Lomonosov in 1761 A.D", "incorrect_answers": ["Galileo Galilei in 1702 A.D.", "Pythagoras in 546 B.C.", "Giovanni Cassini in 1790 A.D."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Piazza San Marco (St Marks Square), which Napoleon allegedly called The drawing room of Europe, is the principal square of this Italian city.", "correct_answer": "Venice", "incorrect_answers": ["Florence", "Rome", "Milan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1891, this successful Ohio City businessman made Americas first gasoline-powered automobile.", "correct_answer": "Lambert", "incorrect_answers": ["Durant", "Duryea", "Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of the popular tile game, Dominoes, often considered to be the modern descendant of the dice, originated from which of these?", "correct_answer": "Domino masks", "incorrect_answers": ["Domino parties", "The name of the town it was created in", "Chinese word for tiles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these New York City neighborhoods did the American Airlines Flight 587 crash on November 12, 2001?", "correct_answer": "Queens", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bronx", "Brooklyn", "Manhattan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of bread is the German bread variety called Dampfnudel?", "correct_answer": "White bread", "incorrect_answers": ["Flatbread", "Black bread", "Whole-grain bread"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Low doses of antidepressants can be used to treat fibromyalgia patients.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]